hello my name is Karina welcome back to
another episode of hermitcraft as you
can see behind me I have been digging
out the bunker for the architects in the
game of demise however I started to mine
and it was starting to take a little
while and then I remembered I have these
lots of blocks of TNT that I've still
done nothing with so I've decided to
plot out every single point two blocks
apart and open it up and put a TNT
inside each of them
so I think and I hope that this will
make things go a little bit faster now
if I've done this correctly it shouldn't
cause a massive Chain Reaction it should
blow an exact hole like that so all I've
got to do is side step
and just right click
[Music]
oh there was a little Chain Reaction
there
oh oh no
oh okay
there was a little bit of lag there
there was a little bit of lag there that
could have been the end of Green I think
carefully is the key word for this
carefully
and start the Chain Reaction off again
well I've got to say this is definitely
faster that's that's for sure this
technique is definitely faster the only
problem is when there's gravel I've also
got to say this is a lot more dangerous
I can hear it all going off behind me
yeah it might have made it quicker but
it hasn't made it that much quicker so
let's do a quick little time lapse get
this all exploded and then we can start
making the real bunker underneath the
shopping district that should save us
from
our own demise
so I started off doing this in a grid
pattern and it worked really well you
can see how clean the explosions left
this area but then I got very quickly
bored and just decided to add loads of
TNT everywhere and it created a mess but
what I really want to do is get isk out
in on this project and Mumbo to help me
out so I'm gonna go over to the
architect meeting room to see iskal
while we're waiting for iskau why don't
we make some slight improvements to my
chair I want it to be big this is going
to be like an Emperor's Throne look at
that this girl's little chair there
mumbo's demoted button his hat his
chat's still up there so I reckon if I
go up here I can make a few more
adjustments to this green yes hello
hello hello hold on just doing some
changes to my chair I don't know if I'd
have to come up there to be honest are
you you have to be honest though are you
are you alive still
please say you're alive dude yes I'm
still alive I don't know if I trust you
oh my goodness what is that chair
it's my new jet no look I'm alive I'm
alive wait why are you wearing my face
um well I I thought that if you were
dead you wouldn't want to trap yourself
this kind of weird this distraction I
mean that is looking pretty good yeah I
know it's his looking kid my chair looks
stupid silly now oh you know it's it's I
think it's the right size wow okay so
this is um an architect meeting without
Mumbo again yep classic I mean look at
that look at the roof yeah he still has
he's not allowed back in here until he's
fixed this
so the reason I've asked you here is
because you know the game of demise
obvious that you were checking if I was
alive yes we need a safe room and like a
panic room that we can go to in an
emergency because obviously I don't
think anyone's dead as far as I'm aware
no one's died so no one there's no
threat at the moment but I'm being
proactive in making an architect bunker
okay oh Underground
but I need some like red Stoney help but
I've started making it do you want to
come see it yes yes all right follow me
has anyone told you that you look a
little bit like Winnie the Pooh yes and
I'm owning it come on piglet
this is the entrance to the bunker uh
it's underneath the diamond pile because
no one's ever gonna touch these diamonds
right
well hopefully not yeah okay and this is
yeah this is it Oh I thought they were
gonna show me like a super high-tech
entrance no this is it this looks
amazing dude wow I love this done this
is only the entrance
this is what I've been working on and
there's it's killing me this is a
massive underground room which I would
like some help turning into our
architect bunker safe room I love it I
absolutely love it this reminds me of
the good old G team yes G team days yeah
exactly I love it so I've created two
beacons here which hopefully will give
strength and resistance but the thing is
if they're just on they're gonna give
away the location of the bunker so kind
of need like a panic button that turns
them on and releases the uh like opens
them up to the air so in in a bad
situation we run down here we hit the
button we get our strength and regen and
we run into the safe room over here
that's the plan anyway this I'm hoping
will be a big space where we can like
create traps so obviously I'm being a
little bit ahead of the game because
when the dead teams start like leaving
traps everywhere if they try and like
get inside here to lay a trap we'll have
traps of our own oh yeah that's the
whole purpose this is a proper safe room
so I'm like I'm imagining it actually I
don't want to give away all my secrets
in case you die
you're a friend but you're also
potentially an enemy yeah don't don't
give away any secrets but I kind of get
the idea Mumbo and mumbo's gonna be like
what's going on guys
yeah he's got he's come on travels he
signs up for the demise game and then he
disappeared I mean that's that's the
best way not to die
is to just not turn up
that is it is
you're not earning any diamonds either
but okay so emergency emergency beacons
is what you need help with yeah and the
entrance the entrances are the entrance
as well I'll be honest I haven't got the
design for this room all figured out yet
but just clearing this out is most of
the work done actually building it up is
gonna take way less time
and it seems in the time that I've been
off the server the iskal's already done
a panic button but again he's not
labeled it what is it with him and not
adding signs
he might have actually added an entrance
as well but I'm not actually sure how
you open it maybe that would have been
useful information as well iskel because
look there's some Redstone here I'm not
sure if this this has got to be related
unless this is just to do with the
beacon stuff anyway let's label this
panic button there we go panic
I
think if you click it
they should come on yes okay so we got
speed resistance and taste of course
from another Beacon so that is pretty
much what we needed the last thing we
need is a proper entrance into this
place that is excellent iskal did that
really really quickly
so we've got the first room to the
demise bunker by Architects but I kind
of want to wait for Mumbo to get back as
well just so he can get involved or not
we'll see but speaking of demise I have
an idea a very um a good idea you see no
one's died in the game of demise and I'm
a little bit surprised it's been a week
shall we say it's been yeah it's been a
week and no one's died well I think we
can do something to encourage this now
as an alive person myself I can't go
around just pvping or laying traps
because that's not the point however
there is a rule in the demise game that
says Mini-Game deaths count as deaths
so we're going to make a little mini
game that they can't refuse
it's going to be glorious let's head
over to the minigame district and start
making this little thing now we're gonna
make this little area right here seeing
as we've got the demise game there we've
got dig straight down we've got my
Mansion which I've still not finished
yet we are going to make it right here
in this space
so what are we going to make here well
this is going to be called demise dares
and basically I'm going to challenge
people to do really dangerous things in
exchange for a lot of diamonds the
problem is there are very few Hermits
that actually need diamonds a lot of
them have more diamonds than they can
ever ever get their hands on and I
myself probably don't have that much to
invest in this so it might work but what
this will do is kick off demise a little
bit faster so the games we're going to
set up are going to be extremely
difficult and it's going to be random
based on this dispenser so I'm gonna put
in a bunch of different challenges in
here and whoever gets in touch and wants
to make some diamonds well it's gonna be
random which one you gotta do so I've
got a few games in mind and not all of
them fit on this space only two of them
will actually fit right here but it's
going to be interesting nonetheless and
I think what's most interesting about
this is that I'm actually I'm going to
do these mini games myself they're not
even mini games I'm gonna do the dares
myself risking my own life to make sure
that these are possible in game and then
it's up to everyone else
to see if they want to do them so this
could backfire this could backfire a lot
I've got three challenges in mind to
start with these are just the ones that
I've been able to think of off the top
of my head and two of them can be done
here and one of them has to be done
somewhere else so we're gonna test these
two first
so the first one we're going to try is a
slightly easier one if you know what
you're doing all of these need to be
possible which is why I'm going to test
them myself now this one is extremely
dangerous but if you know how to fly you
should be able to to nail this quite
easily so I've just got to put some lava
in here now the goal of this is simple
all you got to do is fly through the
tube fly through the tube successfully
and get out the other side if you fall
in the lava the chances of you dying are
pretty high so this is the first dare
that I'm gonna have to try out right
let's get rid of everything
let's get rid of everything we won't
need a totem of undying where we're
going we've got to test this legit
because if it's not possible then I
can't be doing this as a dare Okay so
we've got to fly through the tube fly
through the you know it's it's
I'm scared I'm I'm scared
it's not easy to fly that close to lava
in a one by one hole okay
maybe I should have tested this without
the lava because I'm actually putting my
own life on the line here okay so the
key for this is to just line up properly
okay dare number one completed this one
can now go in the dispenser oh my heart
my little heart fly through the tube
there we go that's the first dare
completed I'm gonna complete all of
these myself just to prove to you that
they're possible and encourage other
people so the next one is very similar
to scars minigame and I'm gonna put all
of these scaffolding up in one by one
tower now it's so ugly that I'm gonna
take it down and put it up whenever
someone wants to play this game because
I mean look at that this is the kind of
thing you don't want on your Minecraft
server so let's get rid of all of these
put it as high as it can go this should
be enough that's that's definitely tall
enough that if that may even be too high
all right here we go so what we got to
do here
is pretty simple we have to fly all the
way to the top or climb all the way to
the top and from here
what we need to do is we grab our total
totem of undying
we're gonna throw it and then we're
gonna go and catch it and then if you
catch it you can then successfully
hit the ground now we definitely need to
make that shorter because I that was a
little bit too easy
whew or maybe you've got to wait two
seconds in order to do that so I'm
actually gonna have to buy a few of
these totem of undying but I've just
proven that number two dare is possible
so here's the prize pool it's going to
be
50 diamonds per win so if you complete
all of the dares you get
150 diamonds
and I'm gonna say this it's only one
attempt per person and it's it's it's
only for alive people by the way you
can't have any of the any of the people
that have gone in demise it's only the
people on the alive list that get to
play this game but look at that that is
a substantial amount of diamonds on the
line just to play my little game all
right there's one more demise there that
I want to set up wow okay I definitely
need less of those it's raining
that looks really cool okay so there is
one last demise dare which is
particularly difficult now there is a
technique to each and every one of these
challenges as well so maybe just two
stacks of those will do and we're gonna
need
a couple of these two in here and one
for me okay so that's two out of three
so we need to add that one catch the
totem so the last one we can't actually
do in this world we can't do this in the
Overworld at all and if you have any
ideas for more demise dares let me know
and I will think about them and possibly
add them to this game because remember
it's going to be completely random what
you get so it'll just be a case of
pressing the button and you get whatever
one you get so catch the totem or fly
through the tube so this is going to be
a lot of fun I hope that some Hermits
will give it a go so the last one that
we need to do is actually in the end but
first I found some more of these
treasure tokens and since I'm spending a
lot of diamonds yeah we got it oh no I
threw both of them at the same time
I'm not even sure how I did that yeah we
want a diamond
okay well I just wasted a token so let's
head over to the void I don't know why
but every time I go back to the nether I
have to use this portal I just I should
probably use the one closest to me now
I'm scared testing these and I know the
tricks on how to beat them so I can't
imagine what everyone else is gonna feel
so we gotta go into the end portal which
is just over here jump into the end man
this place is a mess
now this one is going to be a dangerous
really dangerous so what we need here is
a platform because what we're going to
be doing
is sending them over the edge
over the edge of the island okay
now this one's pretty hit or miss on
whether you make it out alive
now just in case I do die I don't want
to lose my my tools
okay okie dokie
right so basically what you need to do
is you see this coordinate here this is
your Y which means you're up and your
Downs the the task on this one is to
make this hit minus 50 and then get out
yeah yeah you need to hit minus 50
meaning you're gonna jump in the void
and then let yourself fall down and as
soon as you hit minus 50
. you gotta get out again
now you start taking damage very soon
after that so
if you mess up
that's what happens you you die
basically
oh it's too scary okay I did just do it
but we're gonna do it again
yeah
okay
we made it so we have now done all three
of did I annoy him
I'm gonna take my stuff
um I'm Gonna Leave
I'm gonna leave as soon as I can
wait how do I leave oh thank goodness
yeah he's definitely after me
oh and we're back here oh brilliant okay
so that is the third demise dare that
we're going to do and I've just proven
to everyone
that all of these are possible without
dying I just did them first time right
in front of your eyes so now all we need
is maybe a few more ideas and a couple
more customers okay so I've made a
little bit of a sign here saying welcome
to demise dares are you still alive in
demise are you running low on diamonds
contact green for some dares each dare
wins 50 diamonds now I've been waiting
for people to get in touch about demise
dares because I really do want to see
someone try us but it doesn't look like
it's gonna happen this episode however I
have come up with another little
challenge now this one this one's gonna
make me panic this one's gonna make you
panic a lot so what we gotta do is
create
um well a very dangerous situation and
we do that by making a little box of
white glass and we gotta make this
about 10 blocks high so once we've built
this high enough what we've got to do is
actually create a big aquarium and then
we cover the top with some ice at the
bottom we place magma blocks with just
one space left over at the door
and then all we've got to do now is add
water all the way along here and we work
our way all the way up to the top to
fill this in
that should do it so we've got lots of
magma Bubbles and it's going to drag
them down okay so the challenge here is
they've got to go inside and all they've
got to do is break free but they've got
to do that without any anything on at
all so let's get rid of all our stuff
I really should have tested if this
actually works
uh well we'll we'll see if it works one
way or another pretty sure you'll be
able to get out of this okay so they got
nothing on them and all they got to do
they gotta run in obviously there's the
but there's the bottom there that isn't
actually magma blocks and then you've
got to break your way out
oh no
this is taking too long
this is taking way too long
no no no no
oh my goodness
okay so you have to have major Faith
because if you start bailing yes you can
get your oxygen back with the magma
blocks but you'll end up being on the
floor taking damage
this is horrible
this is a really horrible one I love it
Okay so we've proved that that works
that could have really backfired I was
sure I wasn't gonna make it out oh boy
this whole thing could have backfired
horribly okay
we have officially got four dares now
it's very unfortunate that no one's
actually been on the server to come and
have a go at my demise dares but I'm
guessing in the next episode someone's
gonna come along and definitely want
some diamonds so we're gonna add this
last one
into the dispenser
and that is done so hopefully by next
episode we will get maybe one or two
people to come and try the demise dares
now I have proven rather stupidly I
might add that these work and are
possible but are the Hermits
other Hermits gonna survive hopefully we
can encourage a few people on the alive
team to join the dead team but obviously
we're not actually on the dead team
which is why we're doing this as a mini
game this is genius now uh as an alive
person I'm not allowed to like PVP or
trap or anything like that because
that's you know kind of not the point of
the game but making a mini game that
involves death and you know offering
some diamonds that's totally fair that's
that's fair game they know exactly
what's going on here they know they know
what's going on and I think this is
going to end up being really really fun
so Hermits I challenge you to a game of
dares and I'll see you in the next
episode where hopefully we see if they
can do it good bye